Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Get your pig faces away from me!
Tired, my friend?
It's only water,
but you can have some.
I see you're not armed.
It's not healthy traveling
around these parts without a gun.
How are you doing for money?
Good. Pratt never refuses a deal
when it comes to helping a man in trouble.
I'll take your 20 dollars
and you take the empty pistol. Happy?
What did you say your name was?
Looks like you're the silent type.
Whatever your name is,
you've made a serious mistake.
Never turn your back on Pratt.
My name is Pecos.
MY NAME IS PECOS
Bury him.
Well, Smith?
Nothing.
It spluttered something this morning,
stopped and hasn't spoken since.
I've been waiting for news from San Antonio
since yesterday.
Dammit, Smith! The telegraph
is this town's only way to contact Laredo.
We have to move out of here
like everyone else.
I don't want to leave my daughter Mary
in this cesspool.
You've got to make
your damn machine work!
I'm doing what I can, Doctor.
Look, I'll try again.
- Good morning, Dr. Burton.
- There's nothing good about it, dear.
Don't be angry, Dr. Burton.
The rangers will come, you'll see.
Everyone in this town is on edge.
They can't wait to leave.
The barrel of rum!
You go inside.
We've got enough trouble already.
Don't kill him.
Go and get him.
You made us run, Brack.
Quick, go to the wagon.
Huh? Cat got your tongue
after all that running?
Don't tell us you thought
you'd keep all the money for yourself.
80,000 dollars just for you,
without sharing it with your friends.
That's not very nice, Brack.
It's empty, Brack.
When we cleaned out the bank in Laredo,
it was full.
We shouldn't have trusted
a damn bastard like you.
- Where were you planning on going?
- Go to hell!
Idiot.
What good's a dead man to us?
If the money's not in the bag…
it must be somewhere else.
Search the wagon.
Nothing, Kline.
It's empty.
Damn them!
They played us for fools.
Must have hidden it
when we were waiting at the ford.
Bert, Alex.
Keep an eye on this hellhole.
We'll follow the wagon tracks.
Saddle up.
He's back.
- The dirty rat.
- Calm down, Papa.
It doesn't do any good.
You're just hurting yourself.
I'll only calm down when somebody
gives that murderer what he deserves.
We're quits, Alex.
Pay up.
It wasn't that easy in San Juan,
but I always pay my dues.
I've always hated the telegraph.
You sit over there.
Towns without a sheriff
are much more hospitable.
Houston's never had sheriffs.
The winters are too damp,
and the summers are too hot.
Exactly.
You're right, Alex.
You killed five in eight months.
That's pretty quick.
You didn't even make them suffer.
And Morton recited them all
his final sermon.
Morton?
Who's that?
There's Morton.
They're never still,
even when they're dead.
The sons of evil are lost because
your right hand crushes all enemies, O Lord.
Stop, Lucifer!
We're not finished yet.
I've never seen an ill omen like that.
Reminds me of a vulture.
Horrible.
Tedder's paying for this, right?
Of course, my friend. I'm all for the law,
and the law is the barrel of your pistol.
That's how we live just fine
without a sheriff.
- Where are you going?
- He's my brother Ned.
Been here a few days.
He's never owned a gun —
that's why I still have a brother.
The same merry mother!
That's Mr. Gordon from Laredo.
I don't want
to cause you any trouble, boys.
We're all calm in here.
Off you go, beauty.
Yes, I mean you.
Bring us something to eat.
Go on.
Do as I say,
and you might live to tell the tale.
If all goes well, we'll take a vacation
with Kline across the border.
And if anyone plays any tricks,
we'll set this place on fire with you inside it.
They drink too much here?
- Tequila.
- What?
Tequila.
I don't know if…
Look, you're Mexican,
and we don't have any drinks for Indians.
In fact, Indians can't even drink.
Right, Bert?
Why not try
drinking your donkey's piss?
Go on, try it.
I'm thirsty.
You hear that, Bert? He's thirsty.
What can we do?
I'll have a go at him.
You up for that?
No, it's too easy.
Mexicans don't count.
But this one's different.
He's armed.
You can all see the bastard's armed.
Maybe he robbed a dead man.
Seeing as you've got a gun,
Mexican…
let's see if you know how to use it.
No, I don't want whiskey.
I don't like it.
I said I want tequila.
Tequila.
Tequila, please.
Your days are numbered, stranger.
They were two of Joe Kline's men.
They need you in there.
No, my friend.
I don't touch Kline's men.
They're more dangerous
dead than alive.
We're wasting time.
It's no use searching.
There are only spiders
and red ants here.
Let's go back, Kline.
Sooner or later,
the rangers will be on our backs, too.
How can you find a bag
in a thousand square miles of desert?
That swine must have gone to Houston
in the wagon.
Why, when he could
cross the border?
Because he was working for someone.
That's why.
We're staying here
until we've found the money,
rangers or no rangers.
With Houston as our base.
And if one of us
has five aces in his hand,
he can consider himself dead.
What are you doing here?
You like cemeteries?
The Lord doesn't speak
only through Moses,
but through his pastors, too.
I'm ready to recite any kind of sermon,
even ones not in the Bible.
Don't you believe me?
You're mistaken not to trust Morton,
stranger.
Everyone comes looking for me
sooner or later.
A Mexican, you said?
Yes, a Mexican.
They'd already drawn their pistols,
but he was quicker.
I don't know how it happened, Kline,
believe me.
Strange. Those two could do
anything with a pistol —
anything except eat it —
and a lousy Mexican killed them?
This whole business stinks.
You know me, Tedder.
You know I keep my promises.
You can bet your whole filthy hovel
against a dollar
that I'll catch that Mexican.
And when I catch him
I'll rip out his soul.
If I find out that you've helped him,
you might as well blow your brains out
before I get back.
Black, Bud, Emerson.
You stay here. Go easy on the whiskey
and keep your eyes open.
Let's go and take a look around.
Girl!
They've found the bodies,
and they're looking for you.
You can't stay here.
Three of Kline's men are inside.
I don't want them to kill you.
We both want the same thing.
What's your name?
Esther.
Where are you from, Esther?
Boquilla, across the border. My people
work on the land between the mountains.
There's my father,
my sister Lola and my little cousin.
I've worked here for three years.
It's hard, but I eat.
Does the trapdoor by the cellar
still work?
Yes, but how do you know about it?
I know a lot about this village.
I've seen people
being born and dying.
And now?
More are going to die.
This is the best I can do for you.
Tortilla.
- Put it here.
- Bring me a plate, too.
Make sure it's all ready
when the others get here.
You didn't see anything outside,
bitch?
Watch out.
Why are you frightening the girl,
Black?
Slip into my bed, girl,
and you'll be safe.
Didn't they tell you?
All the girls who trust Bud are safe.
Go down to the cellar
and bring my wine, Tedder.
Go on, move!
Come here, Black.
Let's have some fun.
Look.
Don't you like the show?
- Leave her alone, you cowards!
- Wait.
Wash her first.
Mexican women are always dirty.
Let her go!
Cowards!
You were right.
We need to wash her first.
Hello, boys.
Where the hell
did this other Mexican pig come from?
Just imagine
if he's the rat Kline's looking for.
Right.
It may well be him, boys.
That sure is a miracle.
Kline's getting a sore backside
searching for this filthy bastard
and he just falls into our hands.
He's either very stupid
or very smart.
Spit out your name, Mexican.
There's no point.
Dead men can't hear,
and you're a dead man.
My name…
is Pecos.
There's some good wine
down there in the cellar.
A very precious wine.
Filthy bastard!
Those damn bastards will kill him.
Come away from there, Doctor.
Nobody can help him.
Ned's right, Papa.
When the rangers come,
we'll have justice, you'll see.
If I only I could handle a pistol…
or use a stick of dynamite.
Calm down, Papa.
It has to end one day.
Ace of clubs.
Five dollars.
See?
Even your brother Tedder's in cahoots
with that murderer, you know.
But Tedder had no choice.
When Murchison died,
you know where Tedder got the money from
to take over the saloon.
From Kline's pockets, I know.
Right, Ned?
I was a doctor in Dodge City,
when they brought me
a man from Kline's gang.
He was bleeding all over
and full of lead.
I tried to get him back on his feet,
but he was pretty much dead
when they brought him in.
I did my duty as a doctor…
but I didn't manage to save him.
But he was Kline's man,
and one day Kline came to town.
Here.
Look at my hands.
Kline broke my fingers one by one
with the butt of his pistol.
"And now you'll remember Kline,"
he told me,
"whenever you try
to cure somebody."
Papa.
Oh, Papa.
That's enough.
We've had enough fun.
And wasted…
too much time.
You've lost some money, too, right?
What do you know
about that business?
Interfering busybody!
Where's the 80,000 dollars?
In a safe place.
What do you mean?
Go on, answer me.
Talk!
I was on the track
when the wagon arrived.
I saw a man throw a sack in the canyon
at Horn Peak.
You know the rest.
And who are you?
Just a Mexican.
I can see that.
There are too many Mexicans,
even in Mexico.
That's what I think.
Something wrong with your throat?
You've got two sharp eyes,
Mexican,
and I'll close them pretty quick.
Maybe he was telling the truth and that pig
Brack was working with this lowlife.
That could be it.
- Genko?
- Yes, Kline.
Lock him up
and don't let him out of your sight.
We're going to take a look
at the canyon.
We need to follow
the wagon tracks again.
There aren't any tracks, Kline.
If a wagon came by here,
I'll eat my boots.
Look carefully.
Nothing, Kline.
No footprints.
That Mexican lied to us.
Let's go back to Houston.
I'll make him spit out his soul.
He must have told you something.
You Indians
sniff each other out like dogs.
The other night…
I saw you talking to him
the other night.
I see everything at night.
"Look into the darkness,"
the Bible says,
"and your eyes will seek out the light."
But Morton knows some things
that aren't written, girl.
They say I'll do anything for money,
even good things.
Why make trouble for yourself?
That man
doesn't have much breath left.
So… do you want
to tell me who he is, girl?
That way, at least he'll have his name
on his tombstone.
Anyway, when Kline gets back…
he'll kill him.
Pecos!
Come with me.
I know a safe place.
Hurry, Papa!
On the sofa, Esther.
Come here, boy.
They've given you a nasty beating.
- Mary.
- Get some water.
Quick, Mary.
There.
You can't stay in the village.
I know Kline.
I know him, too.
A lot of blood but nothing serious.
So saddle up and get out of here
before Kline and his men
start searching all the houses.
- Esther can find you a horse tonight.
- No.
No. There's still something I have to do.
I'll leave…
Stay calm, now.
I'll leave your house
but not the town.
Esther, you need to go.
They'll be looking for you too now.
You need to leave right away.
Right away.
Neat work.
The knife's tied to a cord.
To a cord.
Somebody helped him.
We've been tricked.
Very revealing, Steve.
That man is more dangerous
than I'd thought.
We should have killed him
straightaway.
Yes, maybe you're right, Steve.
We should have killed him
without thinking twice.
But next time…
Hey, stop that.
You can get drunk later.
Go and wait outside.
Kline, look up.
- There's a hole in the floor here.
- The cord!
Where's it coming from, Jack?
The spinning wheel.
It was that bitch.
- She was pretending to spin.
- Filthy slut.
I'll give you one minute, Tedder…
and then I'll kill your brother.
One more minute…
and I'll kill you, too.
Answer me.
Where's that bitch?
- I could…
- Where is she?
- I could be wrong, but I…
- Don't worry.
- I'd look for her…
- No!
No, Tedder!
Tell me what you know.
I'd look for her at the old farm
on the road to the pass.
That's where her people live.
Let's split up.
You two go to the border.
You go with Slim.
I want that girl.
Where are you taking that?
I didn't know
you had branch offices in town.
It's for Dr. Burton.
I don't drink.
If I had a dollar
every time you were drunk,
I'd be richer
than the Archbishop of Canterbury.
Once in a while. If you don't drink,
what do you do with your mouth?
You're right.
I'll come with you.
I need to see the doctor, too.
And if you don't object,
I'll carry this to save you the trouble.
Alright.
Come on, Lucifer.
This is your home
whenever you need me.
I can't do much,
but I'm ready to help you.
Don't worry about me.
Thank you.
Thank you for your help.
Someone's coming.
What is it, Tedder?
And you too, Morton. What do you want?
The less I see of you, the better.
Stay away from here.
I'm here to…
Don't get all het up, Doctor.
All I've done
is help Tedder bring you some wine.
You shall tend the Lord's vineyards.
There's nothing against wine in the Bible.
Nothing.
And the wine in this barrel
is really very special.
I don't want to have anything to do with you.
Is that clear?
I don't mean to appeal
to your sense of solidarity, Burton,
but deep down there is something
a doctor and a pastor have in common.
What are you talking about,
you damn vulture?
What wine are you talking about?
What's this all about?
I don't want anything from you.
Get out of here.
It's from my brother Ned, Doctor.
They brought me some good wine
from Boquilla. Excellent wine.
And?
My brother Ned said we need to offer some
to the doctor, and I said why not?
Yes.
As the proverb says,
drink first and then spit it out.
It's so right.
Well, if it's a gift
from your brother, that's fine.
Thank him from me.
Where are those bandits?
Kline and his men aren't in town.
They've gone to find
that Mexican and the girl.
It's going to be hard to find them.
The desert's big
and Mexico's nearby.
I think some have gone looking for them
at Esther's family home.
They'll be back soon.
Don't worry, I'll carry it inside.
I'm not convinced by this business.
Not at all.
I'm not convinced.
If someone came to my house
with a barrel of wine,
my door would be wide open,
but they slammed it in your face.
Aren't people strange?
Or maybe not.
Burton.
Do you value your life
and your daughter's?
What do you mean?
Just what I said.
If you value your life,
get rid of this.
This wine is dangerous.
I don't understand. Tedder's a rogue
and would sell his soul for a dollar,
but he wouldn't go as far
as poisoning wine.
Some things
are more deadly than poison.
Kline's not leaving the village because
he's looking for something that's in here.
If that's the case,
tell us what we need to do.
- We need to get rid of Kline.
- Alright, Pecos.
You have a man who can't use his hands
and two girls at your command.
That's not very encouraging,
but we'll do our best.
- What do you need?
- Do you have any other weapons here?
An old pistol
and a few sticks of dynamite.
That'll do.
I'll write the recipe.
Find anything?
Not a trace, Kline.
He didn't cross the ford.
Let's hope Jack's found the girl.
You two go back to Houston.
- Which way?
- The north road.
Alright.
Are you following us?
We'll take the south road.
I don't want any surprises.
Alright, Kline.
- You didn't see anyone go by?
- No, señor.
Think hard.
Tell us the truth
and don't waste my time.
I asked you where your daughter is.
And if you've seen an armed Mexican
on horseback sniffing around.
He came by a few hours ago.
There's no way you didn't see him.
- I said no, señor.
- And your daughter?
Esther comes here very rarely.
She works for Mr. Tedder.
- Who's she?
- My name's Lola, señor.
Esther's my sister.
Seeing as we're here,
let's have some fun.
Little Lola's not bad.
Slim, you're not her type.
She doesn't like you.
Watch out for the horse.
Go on, Slim!
Slim!
Go for it!
Go on!
- What do you want at this hour?
- I need to talk to you, Frank.
All I have is eight dollars.
It's not much to hire a good horse,
I know,
but I've got to get to Laredo
before nightfall.
Does Tedder know?
No, but my brother's happy
when I'm out of his way, Frank.
- Why haven't you told Tedder?
- Look, I need that horse.
I don't like this.
What are you going to Laredo for?
There are better girls in San Juan
or Boquilla, across the border,
and the Mexican girls will do more for you
than any girl in Laredo.
They give you credit, too!
Give me the horse, Frank.
I want to warn the rangers.
Is your brother in the saloon?
Then listen to me.
I've become very thirsty,
and I want to have a beer.
So I'm going for a drink.
Here's a horse.
If a boy who's slightly out of his head
takes the horse and rides off,
how would I know?
I'm just very thirsty.
Good luck.
Get on your feet.
Where were you off to?
Why don't you answer me, runt?
Pecos!
Don't shout, I can hear you.
Kline's men…
The bastards…
Kline's men killed my brother.
He was only a boy.
I thought you only cared
about money.
Once, Pecos, but not anymore.
When I saw him lying there,
murdered like a dog…
He wanted to run
and warn the rangers.
It's your fault that he's dead.
I can't do anything about it.
Get out of here.
But he did it for Esther.
- For the whole town.
- Really?
And what do you want from me?
Help me get my revenge.
And I'll help you.
Come on, tell me the truth.
Spit it out.
You're talking about the barrel?
There's 80,000 dollars inside it.
Brack and I made a deal.
We'd hide it.
Think what you like, Pecos,
but 80,000 dollars
is a lot of money.
We should have split it,
but Joe Kline killed Brack,
so I put it somewhere safe.
I know. In the doctor's house.
Nobody will think of looking there, right?
Right.
But I want Kline to pay
for my brother's death.
- And I…
- You must kill him.
Only you can do it.
I'll give you Brack's share afterwards.
But watch out for Morton.
He's sold you out once already.
Alright, Tedder. Maybe I will help you.
Now get out of here.
The nine of hearts
and the three of clubs.
Not bad, Kline.
Not bad.
Money. I see a lot of money,
and within reach.
Stop being an idiot
and talk straight.
Queen of hearts.
An idiot? I can read the cards,
and the cards predict the future.
You know what I want to hear.
Rat!
What you're looking for could be…
Here's the two of clubs!
… hidden in a trunk.
No, maybe in a barrel.
Go on.
Well, actually…
Isn't that enough?
Or shall I shoot you in the mouth
and take the money back?
Didn't you think of that,
smart-ass?
Listen to me, Kline.
Shoot him right now.
Shoot him in the mouth.
He stinks.
I've always found him disgusting.
I'm useful to you, Kline.
Why kill me?
Here.
Carry on.
Jack of hearts.
Here's the ace of diamonds.
Well?
Well, I'd shake Tedder up a little.
- Tedder?
- Yes, to make him ring…
like Lucifer's bell.
Talk straight.
For another coin…
I can tell you
the name of the Mexican
who's having fun killing your boys.
I'll pay double. Talk, you lowlife,
and tell me how it's all going to end.
Ace of spades.
Queen of spades.
Pecos Martinez is going to kill you.
The last of those bastards.
Remember.
The cards never lie.
It'll be even easier
when we're face to face.
Not a bad bank.
The dead don't steal.
Damn!
You scared me.
I don't want to scare you.
I want to kill you.
You're joking, right?
I never joke.
No.
No, you're not the type
who would kill an unarmed man.
But you're not a man.
- You're a worm.
- No, Pecos!
Listen.
I'll do whatever you ask.
I'll do anything for you.
I don't want to die.
In the name of the Bible,
don't kill me.
Did you see?
I've got a lot of money. A lot.
Nearly 3,000 dollars.
It's yours. Take it!
You and your money disgust me.
I'll give you one day.
Now get out of here.
Nobody must ever see you again in Houston
or smell your stench.
I won't ask
if you sold me out to Kline
because you'd swear on the Bible
and lie like you always do.
Get out of here.
- Don't move!
- What do you want?
You know very well, you old fool,
and this time you won't get away
with a few broken bones.
Your daughter, I imagine.
Not bad.
But I don't think she's yours,
you old goat.
Nothing in here.
Or in here.
No barrel, no money.
Get out.
All of you, get out of my house.
I don't know what you're looking for,
and I don't want to know.
Go to hell!
Don't worry, he's got a thick skin.
I want to know two things.
And you're going to tell me.
Then you can go and take care
of your father without any more trouble.
Where's the barrel
that Tedder handed over to your father?
And where's the Mexican hiding?
As you can see,
the questions aren't that difficult.
Tedder came and took it back.
You're lying.
Tell us everything you know.
It's for your own good.
If we're going to get along,
you need to tell the truth, girl.
I can make you talk, sweetheart.
I'm sure we'll have some fun.
Tell Kline.
Steve likes seeing people suffer.
Especially women.
But you don't need to worry
if you talk right away.
Not bad at all, that chick.
Do you boys want to deal with her?
I'll let you have her later.
She's all yours for now, Steve.
Alright, Kline.
I've got a good idea.
You're wearing too many clothes.
I'll take them off,
and you can walk around the house naked.
Very good, Steve.
I like her.
You'll serve us and cook for us…
wearing nothing
but a ribbon in your hair.
What do you say, boys?
Isn't that a great idea?
We needed a woman
to take care of us
and Burton's daughter
will do very nicely.
Papa! No!
He wanted to take my gun.
Go on, talk.
You can cry later.
I'm asking you for the last time.
Where's the money?
And where's that Mexican hiding?
Morton told me everything.
I know who he is.
That's enough. Let her breathe a little.
If you kill her she won't talk.
If you don't talk,
you know what we'll do to you.
Tell me where the money is.
And where the Mexican is.
Then your troubles will be over,
I promise you.
No… no!
I don't know where Pecos is,
but I know he'll get even with you.
Murderers!
Start again.
Someone's here.
The bastard's coming.
- Let's give him the welcome he deserves.
- What shall we do with the girl?
Forget her, you fool.
It'll be easier
once we've dealt with the Mexican.
Are you afraid, Kline?
No.
But that man must die.
First he'll tell us
where he hid the money,
then he'll die a slow death.
He must be an old friend of yours
if you treat him that well.
It's an old story that's been going on
for three years.
He's been following me
like a ghost.
We need to send him back to hell.
Bud, distract him.
We'll cover him, boys.
He got hit.
Cover me. I'll try.
Push the girl out.
We'll use her as a shield.
Ladies first.
Hey, Pecos!
Do you hear me?
I hear you, Kline.
What do you want?
I want the money,
and I want it right now.
Then we'll get on our horses
and leave.
Hurry up or we'll kill the girl.
I'll give you one minute
to think it over.
I've already thought it over, Kline.
Watch out, boys.
He's preparing
some kind of nasty trick.
Keep your eyes wide open.
As soon as we've got the money,
I'll fill him with lead.
Quick, bring me that barrel.
It's all in there.
Count it.
80,000 dollars that Brack stole from you
and Tedder hid.
Take it, Kline, and get out of here.
It's there, Kline.
Kline,
how are you going to spend it?
You can't get rid of that red line
that marks your place in hell.
Money's no good to you.
Your fate is settled.
You're finished.
You won't leave Houston alive.
You've played all your cards
and you've lost.
Open your ears, Kline.
The rope left a deep furrow
on your neck,
and I'll finish the hangman's work
with my own hands.
Look, Pecos.
They did hang me, it's true,
but they couldn't finish the dance.
I'll play the music this time.
The rope for me?
For Joe Kline, just for destroying
a lousy family by the name of Martinez?
That was your family, Pecos.
Today, I'll settle my account,
and you'll pay.
- Let me go!
- No, Esther.
It's my duty to kill you, Kline…
by order of the court of Houston.
What will we do with the money?
Build yourselves a bigger cemetery.
api.OpenSubtitles.org is deprecated, please
implement REST API from OpenSubtitles.com