Watch any video online with Open-SUBTITLES
Free Browser extension: osdb.link/ext
Straight into the
lounge, get the door.
Adam Roberts.
This has gone far enough.
We've still got time.
We can call the police.
And say what exactly?
Hello, we killed someone,
brought them back to my house
and now decided it was maybe
a good time to let you know.
We can say he was alive.
We brought him into keep him
warm so we could use the phone,
and then he died
while we were waiting.
Don't play dumb, Simon.
You know as well as I do the
second the police arrive,
no matter what
the circumstances,
tomorrow morning, polling day,
yes, our faces are on the
front page of every newspaper
in the country
accompanied by very, very,
very bad headlines.
Come on, forget what that means
for our careers, our lives,
your family's lives.
What about the party?
All the other candidates
facing election tomorrow.
All the people that
need our party.
We can't let one accident
jeopardize everything.
You think I don't know that?
You think I don't realize that.
There's a phone right there.
If you genuinely, and I
mean, genuinely believe
the best thing to do
is call the police
and tell them what
happened, then do it.
Hello, Bertie Oldcross.
Yes, Ms. Robinson,
I do apologize.
Simon had a slight
red wine accident
and needed a fresh shirt.
The party, they're
wondering where we are.
Nowhere.
Make something up.
We cannot go to that party.
I know, Mrs. Robinson,
I'm looking forward to
celebrating with you too.
What would it look
like if we don't?
We go for an hour, keep
everything settled,
and then sort this
when we get back.
No Bertie, no.
Here he is now, Mrs.
Robinson, all sorted.
We will be with you in 10.
This is all gonna
end badly, Bertie.
We've got to go.
40 minutes, then we'll
say we need an early night
and slip off.
Give him a moment.
Shall we?
Oh.
Please, you're very kind,
but there's no need to
pretend you're here for me.
I know you've really
come for the free booze.
Speaking of which, who was
gonna show me to the bar?
Ah.
Mr. Adeveret?
Oh, Mrs. Robinson.
Did I startle you there.
Just a bit, yeah.
Sorry, I am sorry.
Good final numbers
we had, right.
Fantastic, yeah, thank
you for all your help
during the campaign.
Yeah, help's been superb.
Oh, anything for
Bertie and the party.
You know that, Mr. Adeveret.
And how's the family, all okay?
All good, thank you.
They must be so very proud
of what you're trying to do.
You think Bertie will
say a few words tonight?
Oh, I shouldn't think
so, Mrs. Robinson,
it's been a very long campaign.
Oh, sorry, Mr.
Adeveret, I almost forgot.
Someone actually rang here
just before you arrived.
They said they tried your house,
but you'd already left the
party.
That's the number, they
said you should give them
a call back as soon
as you had a moment.
Who is this?
Oh, yes, it's the head of this.
Right, well, I better
get on and do this then.
Labour head
office, Jonathan speaking.
Oh, hello, Jonathan,
it's Simon here,
Bertie Oldcross
campaign manager,
Scarborough and Whitby.
Ah, glad we've tracked you down.
You're at the Whitby
Social Center?
Yeah, at the end of campaign
party, with the volunteers.
Okay, and Bertie's there?
He is, yep.
Right, I'm
letting you know, Simon,
we got wind of the unfortunate
incident earlier this evening
and for the good of the
party, we have alerted police.
They'll be there soon.
Obviously we'll spin the
story as best we can,
but it's not going to
be the best of times
for you and Bertie.
You understand that
it's crucial we protect
the party from
incidents like this,
especially the day
before general election.
Hello, Laura speaking,
Labour Party, head office.
Hello, it's Simon, Bertie
Oldcross's campaign manager,
Scarborough and Whitby
Ah, fantastic,
thanks for calling back.
Looks like it's going to be
a great day for you tomorrow.
Very promising numbers.
Yes, yes, we're
all very excited.
We've had great
numbers across the country
in our final polls.
So if that's reflected in
the result tomorrow night,
it'll be a special
moment for everyone.
Fantastic.
Yeah, that's fantastic.
So the leadership has started
to identify potential options
for government positions.
Just getting a sense of
what our administration
could look like if
things do go away.
Right.
And based on Bertie's stance
on crime and justice
throughout the campaign,
something that's really
caught the public's attention,
we believe he would be
an ideal option to fill
the minister of state
for prisons position.
Prisons, the
minister for prisons?
Now, obviously
this is all preliminary
and dependent on the
final results tomorrow,
but it's something worth
discussing with Bertie,
as things will start
to move quickly
as the picture becomes
more clear after voting.
Minister of state for prisons.
Yes, so I'll
leave that with you.
Yes.
Yes, thanks for letting me know.
And finally I have to ask,
is there anything you
need to let us know about
going into tomorrow, anything
we need to be aware of?
No, nothing I can think of.
Okay, I'll let you
get back to your party then.
Best of luck tomorrow.
Thank you so much.
Everyone, everyone...
I'd just like to say
thanks to you all and what
an absolute pleasure it's
been getting to know you all
throughout the campaign
over the last few weeks.
And I'm sure all our hard
work will be worth it
when Bertie Oldcross
is elected tomorrow
to represent
Scarborough and Whitby.
Now, I'm sure the man himself
has a few words of his own.
Now I won't say much, I promise,
but now I'm sure you've all
had enough of my voice by now.
Obviously I want to thank
you all for your support
and the time you have
given to my campaign.
Trust me, we couldn't
have done it without you.
And I just want to
say that if the result
goes my way tomorrow,
I will spend every day
making sure our country
is a happier, more prosperous,
safer place to live.
Now it's been a long campaign.
Simon and I have a
very big day tomorrow,
so we're going to
call it a night.
But by all means you stay
and enjoy yourselves.
You've earned it.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, thank you so much.
See you next time.
Simon, Simon.
How'd you do that?
Do what?
Put on that show.
You would tell those lies.
What do you mean,
they weren't lies.
There was a man lying
dead on your sofa.
What is wrong with you?
Would you pull
yourself together?
We could go a prison, Bertie.
Yeah, if I don't act
as I normally would,
then you are right, that is
exactly what will happen.
You know, yours
is the first door
they will knock
on if I'm caught.
We're in this together, Simon.
Just get in.
Thoughts?
I've got saws in the garage.
For what exactly?
You know.
That's disgusting.
No, we just need to
move the thing as is.
We could throw it in the sea.
No, it'll be washed up
on the beach by morning.
We didn't get noticed
throwing it in the water.
No, I need to find
somewhere to bury it
so it'll stay there, somewhere
just to get us past tomorrow.
After the elections, we're
slightly in the clear.
Right.
We're gonna need some shovels.
Hello, Sarah, sweetie, it's
just me leaving you a message
just to say I'm
back at Bertie's.
A few more points we need
to cover for tomorrow,
so I'll be a few more hours.
So don't wait up.
Okay, bye.
I love you.
This was your perfect spot?
It's plenty of land.
It's nice and secluded
and it's all we've got.
Shall we?
Enough?
I really do hope so.
Just hurry up and drag
him there so we can leave
all this behind.
Just calm down.
Tomorrow, everything
will be back to normal.
Normal?
We are stuck in a damn wood
in the middle of the night.
Tomorrow or any other
day for that matter
will not be normal.
Will you keep your voice down?
That was the point of
doing all this, no?
Restoring normality
to make sure
we can get on
with doing what
we set out to do.
I am doing this with
the good of the people,
to make this country a
better place for them.
That is what I care about.
Trust me, it's very
clear what you care about.
I just hope after this,
I can trust you Simon.
I've got more at stake than you.
Oh, well golly for you.
I don't have to listen to this.
Listen, Simon, I'm sorry
for snapping like that...
Hey Bertie Oldcross,
man of the people.
I never forget a face.
Well, well, we are in some
trouble, aren't we Bertie?
You socialist scum.
Just can't help
yourselves, can you?
Let me explain
I'll do the talking, Oldcross.
Me and you were gonna take a
little walk up to the house
and we'll see what the
police make of all this.
The saddest thing of all
is you genuinely thought
you'd get away with
this, didn't you?
This is all your fault.
Just look at this mess.
You made me do this.
That is definitely not
the answer, Simon, come on.
Who cares?
Who cares what the
answer is to any of this?
He fired twice.
There's no shots
left in the thing.
Just look at this mess.
It's all gone wrong.
Just what have we done?
Two guys die tonight
because of us,
because of the choices we made.
We can't do anything
to change that now.
But if we achieve,
if we genuinely deliver,
surely that makes up
for our actions tonight.
Surely.
Just get the shovel.
I know it doesn't
seem like it now but,
I'm certain we made
the right choices tonight.
I don't know we had much
choice in any of this, Bertie.
You know, they actually offered
you minister for prisons.
Yeah.
Party head office rang,
jobs basically on the table.
That's what I
mean though, Simon.
This is a real opportunity.
You know what I'm
thinking Bertie.
I'm thinking what's
best for my family.
You know what my answer is?
Get the election outta the way,
get the all clear on that front
and we'll
reduce the impact a bit.
Then I'm gonna go to the police
and tell them everything.
Reckon I can get around killing
the farmer on self defense.
He had a gun, I had
a shovel, right?
I'm looking at perverting
the course of justice.
Probably get away with no
prison time, coming clean,
handing them you.
That's what I'm
thinking, Bertie.
That is what I am thinking.
You know, here's
what I'm thinking.
I'm sure I can handle
myself for one day.
So you do your thinking
and choose very carefully
what your future is going to be.
If you want to build
something great together,
I'll see you
tonight at the gala.
If you choose not to come,
then our guess I'll know
you've chosen your plan,
and I'll expect to
get a knock at my door
that brings everything
we've worked for,
everything we've
wanted crashing down.
Rough night's
sleep, Mr. Oldcross?
It's a big day.
May I come in.
Please.
To your right.
What can I help you
with then, officer?
Well, Mr. Oldcross,
I'm here in relation to an
incident
that occurred last night
that we have reason to believe
you may have had
some involvement in.
Would you like tea,
officer, hot coffee, maybe?
This is incredibly
serious. Mr. Oldcross.
It would be best if you
cooperated with my inquiries.
Look, I'm not sure where
you got this information from,
but I have a clue what
you are talking about.
All right, now I've got
an incredibly busy day
and I'd appreciate if you didn't
waste any more of my time.
Mr. Oldcross, I'm going to
make this very clear to you.
I'm here because we can
place you at the scene
of a double murder that
took place last night.
Now I'll say it
for a final time,
I strongly suggest
you cooperate.
Okay.
Where do we go from here?
I'll need you to come
with me, Mr. Oldcross.
Shall we, Mr. Oldcross?
This isn't right, Bertie.
This is all gonna
end badly, Bertie.
There's a man lying
dead on your sofa.
What's wrong with you?
Mr. Oldcross,
did you kill
these two men last night?
No, no, please, I can explain.
That's him, all right.
Socialist scum.
Please, please, please.
It's for the best, Bertie.
No, please.
For the good of the
people, right, Bertie?
Rough night sleep. Mr. Oldcross?
It's a big day.
May I come in?
Please.
To the right.
I'm Officer Carrie.
Would you like to take a seat?
Of course, sorry.
Did you cut yourself?
Oh, I get nose bleeds, you know,
I do apologize.
Right, that's unfortunate.
Sorry, it's been
a long few weeks.
What can I do for you?
Mr. Oldcross.
Please, Bertie is fine.
I'm your chaperone for the day?
Chaperone?
Mr. Oldcross, Bertie,
I'll be chaperoning you
to cast your vote.
And later tonight I'll
take you to the count.
I thought you were informed.
Yes, yes, it must've
slipped my mind.
I'll need to change
before we head off.
Great, no problem at all.
I was told your
campaign manager, Simon,
who will be joining us
Is he on his way here or?
He's having the day for himself.
Makes sense.
Yes.
So give me half an hour to
change and we can head out.
Great.
You okay, Simon?
Oh, fine, just got
a lot in my mind.
One too many drinks with Bertie?
Well, you must have
gotten late last night.
Must have been asleep by
the time you got home.
How did everything...
So what's on the agenda today?
Nothing.
Just myself.
Well, you definitely
deserve a rest.
Simon?
Sorry, sorry.
What is it then?
Did something happen
with Bertie last night?
What, no, no,
nothing's happened.
Well, what is it then.
Bertie's offered me a place
with his staff in London.
Which was always
the plan, right?
Well, I thought that'd
be an easy decision.
It is, it is.
If it goes his way, Bertie
offered a ministerial position
in prisons.
I thought you'd be
excited about that, though.
Big role.
It's just more than I expected.
Just gotta get my
head around things.
Right, well, whatever
happens, you know,
we are proud of you
and what you're doing.
Okay.
You're done?
Yeah.
Come on, let's go and
get those teeth brushed,
ready for school then.
Bertie, Bertie, Bertie.
Is this a done
deal for Labour, Bertie?
Have you done enough
to swing this
seat, Mr. Oldcross?
Bertie, how will you
shore up with your campaign?
How are you feeling
about tonight, Bertie?
How'd you sleep
last night, Mr. Oldcross.
I slept very well, thank you.
It's been a long campaign
and I'm glad it's over.
The people of
Scarborough and Whitby
as well as across the
country can finally go
to the polls to
make their choice.
Thank you very much.
Do you have any comments
on missing local
man, Adam Roberts?
I'm sorry?
Adam Roberts, reported
missing by his wife
last night after
failing to return home.
I wasn't aware of that.
The appeal's just gone
out to the local press.
Do you have anything
to say to his family?
Well, as I said, I,
I wasn't aware of it,
but my thoughts of course,
with his wife and family,
and I hope to hear of his
safe return home soon.
Morning Bertie, let's
get you checked in,
then you can cast your vote.
You've just missed
the pre-work rush,
so it's nice and quiet for you.
Has Simon been here?
Turnout looks
pretty good so far.
Obviously we're expecting a bit
of a flurry around lunchtime.
Mrs. Robinson,
has Simon been in?
Then of course after work,
there'll be another rush.
So really, you've
timed it perfectly to
Mrs. Robinson, Mrs.
Robinson, please,
have you seen
Simon this morning?
No, he hasn't been in yet.
Let's get you sorted.
Bertie Oldcross.
ID, please.
Use the booths at the
back, one cross only.
I killed Adam Roberts.
I killed Adam Roberts...
All done?
I won't ask who he voted for.
Over
here, Mr. Oldcross.
Thanks Mr. Oldcross.
Bertie, Bertie
Mr. Oldcross is back
in the vehicle, over.
There's a person
reported missing.
Adam Roberts.
Local press asked if
I had any information.
They've been asked
to put out an appeal.
Right, well, I've got to
go and speak to his family,
get some details.
Right.
So I'll drop you home now,
but I'll be back later to
escort you to the count.
Right, okay.
Okay then.
Come on, Simon, come
on, pick up, please.
Hello, your call cannot be taken
at the moment, so please leave
your message after the tone.
Around the country
are reporting
incredibly high turnouts
in this landmark
general election.
Schools, churches, and community
halls opened their doors
at 7:00 AM this morning
to welcome voters,
determined to have
their say on which party
is most fit to run the country.
Oh, you're in here.
Sit down there with
daddy while I'll go
and get your swimming stuff.
Open their
doors at 7:00 AM this morning
All okay?
Just keeping an eye on things.
Picture of the
Scarborough Gazette.
Bertie is on the front page.
Among the voters were
the candidates themselves,
each visiting their local
constituency polling station
to put the next
Adam Roberts.
I know, awful story.
He just disappeared
last night, apparently.
Alice, sweetie, why
don't you show daddy
that picture he made today
while I'll go sort your
bag, I'll be two minutes.
Did you make this at school?
Yep.
What's this
That's me, that's
mummy, and that's when you
win your competition.
Win my competition?
Yep, for today.
That's definitely one
for the fridge, aint it?
Definitely.
I don't think she knew
what was happening really,
but obviously she's picked
up more than we thought.
So what time do you think
the count will come in?
Just, I thought maybe we could
all go as a family, or
share the moment, you know.
Probably not till
the small hours.
I know, but I'd like
to be there for you then.
And Alice, obviously have
some idea what's going on.
Be nice for us to go
as a family together.
Right, let's get
you to swimming.
Go on, give daddy a hug.
See you later.
On the 1st of July.
They will also face economic
challenges domestically,
a topic which has
led the campaign
of both major parties
throughout the election,
as they seek support in
new parts of the country
for the next millennium,
as well as continuing work
in the Northern
Ireland peace process
as the country moves on from...
To start, I'd like to
thank you for choosing
to put your trust in me.
Dishonesty and selfishness have
become an unfortunate trait
of our politics over
the last few years.
The time has come for change,
and I am both
honored and excited
to be given the
chance to deliver it.
I chose to become a politician
because of my sister, Janet.
Janet was a police
officer, kind and caring.
She wasn't just trying
to enforce the law.
She saw her job as
trying to help the people
in her community in
any way she could.
Janet was my inspiration.
A year and a half,
a year and a half ago,
she was killed on duty
by a man she was arresting
for stealing a purse.
It contained 30 pounds.
30 pounds.
Losing my sister broke my heart.
She was my world, my rock,
and that man took her
life over 30 pounds.
And why?
Because he was desperate.
Desperate to put
food on the table,
desperate to provide
for his family,
desperate to
survive in a society
that had abandoned
him beyond hope,
and it's for that reason,
I had to...
forgive him.
That's why I became
a politician.
I knew I had to find a way
to stop this happening again
to another person,
another family.
Hello, your call cannot
be taken at the moment, so
please leave your message
after the tone.
Simon, I know I said
I'd let you take the day,
give you time and space
to make your own decision.
I want to make sure we both
make the right choice here.
We've got a chance to
really make a difference.
We started this
thing to help people.
We can still do that.
If we only get a year
at this, or a month,
a week even, to me,
it's worth doing.
It's worth doing together.
Simon...
We have Bertie
Oldcross Labour's candidate
for Scarborough and
Whitby in the studio,
ahead of polling day tomorrow.
Thanks Jen.
No, please, thank you Bertie
for spending your
final campaign hours
chatting to us and taking
calls from listeners.
Not at all.
My pleasure.
So Tony Blair's new Labour,
I mean, it's all been
a bit crazy isn't it?
How do you fit into all this?
It's incredible, being at
the center of this whirlwind,
you can really feel
people's excitement.
The campaign's
been a lot of fun.
Oh, well, I mean,
let's be honest,
the election's in
the bag, surely.
It's looking promising, but
until the votes are counted,
anything can happen.
And what about the people
of our wonderful seaside town?
The people of Scarborough
and Whitby have been amazing,
really receptive of our message.
They want change.
That's been made
very, very clear.
And I am the man who
can bring that about.
Right, oh, I'm getting
the word from our producer
that we're ready to
take a few calls.
So should we crack on?
Please.
Okay, on the line is Caroline,
a dinner lady from Whitby High?
All right, Caroline.
Hello.
What's your question
for Bertie, Caroline?
Hi, Bertie.
Afternoon, Caroline.
First of
all, I'd just like to say
how fantastic it is
to see a local face
on all these posters,
such a handsome face too.
Thank you so much, Caroline.
Did you have a
question, Caroline?
Oh, yes, well,
I've lived in Scarborough
all my life.
It's always been a
peaceful friendly place,
but for the first time
in my life, really,
I don't feel very safe.
I'm sorry to hear
that, Caroline.
You know what, listen Bertie,
I do love you, Bertie,
but my granddaughters
walk to school each
morning, scared.
It's an absolute disgrace.
You're right, Caroline,
it is a disgrace.
No one should ever feel
unsafe on our streets,
and I hate to hear that
your granddaughters do.
I promise that a vote for me
tomorrow means we can start
putting more officers on the
ground with better training.
Our children should feel
safe walking to school.
You know, this is a
problem we're seeing right
across the country which
unfortunately is a direct result
of poor social policy by
the conservative government.
To me, everyone is important.
I'll ensure that our
offices truly understand
the local people and
the problems they face.
Now, if we can implement
that across the country,
we will be building a community
that is far better equipped
to serve everyone.
Anything to add, Caroline?
You've definitely
got my vote, Bertie,
and if you do win tomorrow,
I'll go for a swim in the
fountain in my knickers.
Right, thanks there, Caroline.
Moving on,
how do you in intend to pay
for all this Bertie?
I mean, this is pie in
the sky thinking, no?
Jen, everything's laid
out in our manifesto.
Under a Labour government,
no individual will be
overlooked or forgotten.
We won't try to sweep our
problems under the carpet.
That's how I intend to
tackle the rising crime
and how the Labour party
will offer true prosperity
to all the people
of Great Britain.
That was a grand plan, Bertie.
Things can only get better.
Wow, our switchboard
is really lighting up.
So you ready for another caller?
We have Lenny from Barrow Cliff.
All right, Lenny,
what's your question?
Around the United Kingdom...
Numbers looking healthy
going into the polls tomorrow.
Our estimate puts
you at almost 20%.
Same story with the
party across the country,
We're over the line.
Thanks Simon, for everything.
We make a great team.
People love you.
I hope it goes without
saying there's certainly place
for you in my office
at Westminster.
From Scarborough to parliament.
Can't think of anyone
I'd rather do this with.
Well then, old man,
I'd better tell Sarah,
Darling, we are
moving to London.
I shouldn't be too long.
Soon as Alice is in bed,
I'll be back for you.
Please, family comes first.
These end of campaign
parties are just a booze up
for the volunteers anyway.
Oh, I don't think
it's too preemptive
to start familiarizing
yourself with this.
I'll be back around
nine, latest.
Across the country,
reports from our final
polls are flying in.
The Northeast is predicted to
swing heavily towards Labour
in tomorrow's voting with
Durham and Middlesbrough
deep in the red.
The biggest shock is expected
in Scarborough and Whitby
where Labour are polling
at 20 plus points ahead.
It would seem Bertie
Oldcross can do no wrong
in the race for that seat.
Moving down south, we see a
similar picture in London.
We have Tony Blair's Labour
predicted to steal seats
across the capital in what
could be a landslide result
for his party.
To start, I'd like to
thank you for choosing
to put your trust in me.
Dishonesty and selfishness have
become an unfortunate trait
of our politics over
the last few years.
The time has come for change,
and I am both...
honored,
honored and excited to be
given the chance to deliver it.
Honored and excited.
Honored, and excited...
Sorry, I'm a tad late,
ready to rock and roll?
Nearly there.
If you say so.
Did you get a chance
to read it then?
Ah, yes, yes, yes.
And?
A winner as always.
It's strange to think
tomorrow's result,
well, may only be the beginning.
At least tonight
we can celebrate
a campaign superbly run.
True.
Even if you do say so yourself.
Shall we?
Mind if I drive.
Fine by me.
Let's hear it then.
What's that?
The speech obviously.
Well, I'm not sure
I know it all that well yet.
Just bridge
the gaps with anything
that comes naturally.
To start, I'd like to
thank you for choosing
to put your trust in me.
Dishonesty and selfishness have
become an unfortunate trait
of our politics over
the last few years.
The time has come for
change and I am both
honored
and excited to...
Simon.
Look at me, Simon.
This is bad, Bertie.
We need to get help.
Hey, we need to call an
ambulance or the police.
Simon breathe, take a
breath and listen to me.
We are not calling anyone.
Listen to what I'm saying.
We're going to get
this man off the road
and back to my house
where we can make
a proper rational decision
about what we're going to do.
Yes?
No, Bertie, please,
we need to call someone.
Simon, I'm telling you,
we are not calling anyone.
This isn't right, Bertie.
As clocks across the
United Kingdom strike 10
and polls closed for the
1997 general election,
we can give you the
results of our exit poll
from voters around the country.
There it is, 10 o'clock,
voting is now closed
and our exit poll is
predicting a landslide victory
for Tony Blair and
the Labour Party.
Stay with us through the night
as we bring you live results
from constituencies
around the United Kingdom
as counts are confirmed.
Not looking too bad for
you guys as it stands.
Sorry.
The count, it's going
well for your party.
Looks like it could
be a big moment.
Definitely, very exciting times.
So was there any news
about that missing man?
Did his wife say
anything helpful?
I know it sounds
hard, considering,
but I can't actually
say anything to you
Although after tonight, that
may be a different story.
Any sign of Simon.
He didn't come with you?
I left a message
for him when I heard
the result was closed.
I can try again.
No, I'm sure he'll
be here in a minute.
Oh, I'd like to give
a quick thanks to all
of our volunteers for
your speedy work over
the past few hours.
Now we are preparing to deliver,
so if I could get all
candidates to the stage
so we can proceed, please.
Thank you.
Righty-ho, all here.
Good stuff, good stuff.
So in a moment I'd
like you all to step
onto the stage and line
yourselves up at the back,
at which point I will proceed
to announce the vote count
for each candidate and finish
by confirming the winner.
All clear so far?
Perfect.
Now we have been notified
that our declaration
will be televised,
okay, very exciting,
and the winning candidate
will be invited obviously
to say a few words
at the microphone
once the formalities of the
declaration have been fulfilled.
All clear?
Okay, if you'd like to
step onto the stage,
we are ready to declare.
Good luck to you all.
As Scarborough and
Whitby returning officer,
it is my duty to return
the result for the election
held on May 1st, 1997, for
this parliamentary seat.
The total number of
votes cast were 54,321.
The results are as follows:
With 2,191 votes, Jane
Toole, the Referendum Party.
With 7,672 votes, Tony
AHL-DEH-BRAH, Liberal Democrat.
With 19,667 votes, Joe
PIHK, Conservative Party.
With 24,791 votes, Bertie
Oldcross, Labour Party.
Labour win the seat!
To start, I'd like to
thank you for choosing
to put your trust in me.
Dishonesty and selfishness have
become an unfortunate trait
of our politics over
the last few years.
The time has come for change.
And for this reason I must
make a confession.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org